https://www.intercosmetics.ca/page/privacy-policy

Cart
Your cart is empty.
Text
"{{option.copy}}"
{{key}} : {{style}},
Selected Options
{{option}},
Product Addons for
()
Total
Your cart is empty.
Empty Cart
Please log in!
1-800.263.4333
For Customer Service.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us! Intercosmetics is committed to respecting your privacy through the protection of your Personal Information. We only collect your personal information for the purpose of accessing features of this website, such as online shopping.
The following outlines our pledge to you:
Purpose and Consent: Before collecting your Personal
Information, or at the time of collection, we will explain to you the
purpose of collecting it and obtain your consent.
Limiting Collection: Our collection of Personal
Information is limited to what is reasonable under the circumstances and
your information will be used only for the purpose for which it is
collected.
Security: Your Personal Information is kept
confidential and secure and is not disclosed to anyone outside our group
of companies and our selected third party service providers/business
partners without your consent, unless required by law.
Access: You have the right to access your own
Personal Information, and to correct any inaccuracies.
INTERCOSMETICS WILL NOT STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
INTERCOSMETICS SELLS ESTHETIC EQUIPMENT AND SUPPLIES TO PROFESSIONAL TRADE ONLY. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REQUEST PROOF OF BUSINESS.
THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED BY US ON AN "AS IS" BASIS. THIS WEBSITE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS WEBSITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, THIS WEBSITE DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE OWNERS OF THIS WEBSITE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.
Security
SECURITY FEATURES ARE IN EFFECT FOR THIS STORE. THIS SITE IS REGISTERED WITH VERISIGN AND PROTECTS INFORMATION THROUGH STANDARD ENCRYPTION FEATURES. SEVERAL ADDITIONAL UNPUBLISHED SECURITY FEATURES ARE IN ALSO EFFECT.
SignUp For Our eNewsletter
Submit
Shopping Links
Account Login
Register an Account
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Intercosmetics © 2020. All Rights Reserved.
